<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<div>
	<p>Though Durant's height is officially listed as 6 ft 9 in (2.06 m), he has stated that he actually stands 6 ft 10 3⁄4 in (2.10 m) barefoot and 7 ft 0 in (2.13 m) with shoes. His primary position is small forward and his career averages are 27.2 points, 7.2 rebounds, and 3.8 assists per game. Widely regarded as one of the best players of his generation, Durant has earned All-NBA honors seven times (2009–14, 2016–17) and was voted Rookie of the Year in his debut season. He has also won an MVP Award and finished second in the voting three times, a trend that he has expressed frustration over.</p>

	<p>Durant is best known for his prodigious scoring ability. From 2010 to 2014, he won four scoring titles, becoming one of only two players to win four scoring titles in a five-year span. Early in his career, his playing style was isolation-driven, but he quickly developed into an excellent off-ball player who was capable of scoring from the outside as well. By 2013, he was shooting at a historically-great clip, which helped him become one of only seven members of the 50–40–90 club. This ability to impact the offense in a variety of ways helped Durant remain effective and improve an already elite offense upon joining the Warriors in 2016.Throughout his career, his height and 7 ft 4 in (2.24 m) wingspan have created matchup problems for defenses as he is able to get off a clean shot regardless of the situation. Upon beating his man or gaining momentum, he also becomes a strong finisher at the rim; for example, he converted 72.2% of shots in the paint in 2012.</p>

	<p>Early in Durant's career, he was criticized for his slim build, defense, and passing. Over time, he grew as a playmaker, increasing his assist numbers every year from 2010 to 2014, though his overall vision still lagged behind the league's best passers'. He also showed defensive improvement, with opponents averaging just .62 points per isolation play against him in 2014, the best success rate for defensive players who faced at least 100 isolations that season. Upon going to Golden State, he developed into a more reliable off-ball defender and rim protector, and in 2018 was considered for the Defensive Player of the Year Award.</p>
</div>